like say welcome brothers and sisters to
another Wednesday question and answer
well we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep brother tanzel and
God spake all these words saying I am
the Lord thy God which have brought thee
out of the land of Egypt out of the
house of bondage thou shall have no
other gods before me thou shall not make
unto thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above or that is in Earth beneath or
that is in the water under the Earth
thou shall not bow down thyself to them
nor serve them for I the Lord thy God am
a jealous God visiting the iniquities of
the fathers upon the children un the
third and fourth generation of them that
hate me and showing Mercy unto thousands
of them that love me and keep my
Commandments thou shall not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain for the
Lord will not hold him Guiltless that
take of his name in vain remember the
Sabbath day to keep it holy six days
shall thy labor and do all thy work but
the seven day is the Sabbath of the Lord
thy God and it thou shall not do any
work thou nor thy son nor thy daughter
thy man's servant nor thaty maid servant
nor thy cattle nor thy stranger that is
within thy gates for in six days the
Lord made Heaven and Earth the seat and
all that in them is and rested the
seventh day wherefore the Lord blessed
the Sabbath day and hollowed it honor
thy father father and thy mother that
thy days may be long upon the land which
the Lord thy God giveth thee thou shall
not kill thou shall not commit adultery
thou shall not steal thou not bear false
witness against thy neighbor thou shall
not covet thy neighbor's house thou not
cover thy neighbor's wife nor his man
servant nor his maid servant nor his Ox
nor his ass nor anything that is thy
neighbors we read Exodus
21-17 may the Lord have a blessing to
the reading of his word in Jesus name we
pray amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time keep in mind that
all vague questions will not be answered
and all long scripture questions will
not be answered for time sake but we may
be able to point you in the direction of
a DVD or CD that you can purchase by
calling office so please be as direct as
possible with your questions so we can
be as direct as possible with our
answers out of the King James Bible no
other Bibles will be acknowledged on
this program also keep in mind that this
is a live stream you may begin to send
in your questions at this time even
questions that pertain to everlasting
life we just asking that you keep your
questions to a two scripture maximum but
let me introduce to you to family that's
on the panel this evening we got brother
Jerome
Grace and peace Brother Dre good evening
brother Julius good evening everybody
brother tanzel good evening sister
Deborah good evening brother
Sean good
evening and we have the guest caller
with us and I'm brother Cornell sister
Deborah what is our first question of
the evening uh yes there are several
held over questions that will be
answered first before getting into
tonight's uh
Q&A um Zion have two questions his first
question
is explain first corini 7 verses 18 and
19 why does Paul say
circumcision is nothing but the keeping
of The
Commandments and two
the second question is 1 corini 11
verse6 concerning head covering why does
he say we have no
custom all right so brother tenzel let's
go to First Corinthians
7 and pick it up at that verse 18 and 19
on why does Paul say circumcision is
nothing but the keeping of The
Commandments and when you get there go
ahead brother and the guest caller will
take it from from
there is any man called being
circumcised let him not become
uncircumcised is any called in
uncircumcision let him not be
circumcised circumcision is nothing in
uncircumcision is nothing but the
keeping of The Commandments of
God okay we we're going to deal with it
the way it is first thing is Paul is
telling you if you're not circumcised
when you're called don't get
circumcised and if you circumcised when
you called don't become uncircumcised
first thing you can't become
uncircumcised once it's done it's
done but the whole thing
is we going we are going to see what God
and Abraham
did as opposed to what Paul wrote
here because we going to see when
Abraham when was
called was he circumcised or
uncircumcised so we go to Genesis the
17th
chapter and we're going to start reading
at verse n we're going to read from 9
and four to 14 and then we're going to
skip
down that's uh Genesis 17 and verse
9 okay
read and God said unto Abraham thou
shall keep my Covenant therefore thou
and thy seed after thee in their
generation this is my Covenant which ye
which ye shall keep between me and you
and thy seed after thee every man child
among you shall be circumcised and you
shall circumcise the Flesh of your
foreskin and it shall be a token of the
Covenant betwix me and you and he that
is eight days old shall be circumcised
among you every man child in your
generation he that is born in the house
or bought with money of any stranger
which is not of thy seed
he that is born in thy house and he that
is bought with thy money must needs be
circumcised and my Covenant shall be in
your flesh for an Everlasting Covenant
and the uncircumcised
man go ahead finish it and the
uncircumcised Man Child flesh of his
forkin is not circumcised that Soul
shall be cut off from his people he have
broken my
Covenant now I don't know what Paul me
but I'm going tell you something this
come directly from God and then he said
any male child is born must needs be
circumcised so if God says something
must needs be done you can't tell me
that it vealed nothing you understand
what I'm saying and then he said also
whether you born in the house are bought
with money you must need be circumcised
and any male child is not circumcised
shall be cut off from among his people
now this is what God saying okay now
Abraham when God brought it to
Abraham Abraham and nobody in his house
was
circumcised who according to what we
read in Paul's writing he said if you
called an
uncircumcised don't become circumcised
well let's see what Abraham did I want
you to skip down to verse
22 and start reading
and he left off talking with them and
God went up from Abraham and Abraham
took ishmail his son and all that were
born in his house and all that were
bought with his money every male among
the men of Abraham house and circumcised
the Flesh of their for skin in the selfs
same day as God has said unto
him and Abraham was 90 years old and N
when he was circumcised in his flesh of
his
foreskin and ishmail his son was 13
years old when he was circumcised in his
flesh of his foreskin in the self same
day was Abraham circumcised in ishma his
son and all the men of his house born in
the house and bought with money of the
strength who was circumcised with
him
now according to that Abraham broke
Paul's
law because he was uncircumcised when
God enter into that Covenant with him
but according to God's law as soon as
Abraham got through talking with God and
God left up from talking with Abraham
that very same day Abraham got he
circumcised ishmail he circum had
himself circumcised and every male in
his family so now I'm going with what
God Said and what Abraham did Abraham
was uncircumcised when God made the
Covenant and Abraham got circumcised to
come into the law of the company do
now and the Lord said if you're not
circumcised you gonna get cut off so you
can't tell me that circumcised or
uncircumcised Afra of nothing but
keeping of the Commandment look if you
keep the
Commandments and uh uh uh you're not
circumcised according to what the Lord
said you're going to get cut off it's
all
that now so Abraham got Abraham his
whole house were circumcised that very
same day but they didn't stay where they
was called otherwise Abraham would would
have said no I'm I'm not going to do it
CU you call me in in in this call me in
this uncircumcised state so I'm not
going to get out of it so I don't know
what Paul mean but I just showed you
what God and Abraham mean now let's go
to the second one and read
it uh 1 Corinthians 11 verse 16
concerning he covering why does he say
we have no
custom read read verse
16 but if any man seems to be conscious
contentious we have no such custom
neither the Church of
God so now he was talking about when
when Paul was talking about being
circumcised start at the top of that
verse at the top of uh 11 and one what's
it say
be ye followers of me even as I also am
of
Christ go now I Praise You Brethren that
you remember me in all things and keep
the ordinance as I deliver them to you
but I will have you know that the head
of every man is Christ and the head of
the woman is the man and the head of
Christ is God every man praying or
prophesying having his head covered
dishonor of his head
but every woman that pray will
prophesies with her head uncover
dishonor with her head for that is even
all one as if she was
shaven for if the woman be not covered
let her also be shorn but if it be oh
shame for a woman to be Shor or shaven
will let her be covered for a man
indeed now that's enough of that but but
so from what I can understand about this
question
Paul is saying that uh uh uh there's no
custom in Israel that a woman's head
should be
covered well kind of big a different on
that let's go into numbers the 5th
chapter we're going to restart we're
going to start at 14 we're going to read
14 and 15 then we're going to
skip read it when you get there numbers
the 5th chapter verse 14
numbers 5 numbers 5 verse 14 and
15 and the spirit of jealousy come upon
him and he be jealous of his wife and
she be defiled or if the spirit of
jealousy come upon him and he be jealous
of his wife and she be not defiled then
shall the man bring his wife unto the
priest and he shall bring her offering
for her the 10 part of a ephod of barle
meal he shall pour no oil upon it nor
put frankincense thereon for it is an
offering of jealousy an offering of
Memorial bringing iniquity to
remembrance now this is a man this is if
a man is jealous of his wife and he
gonna take him to the priest so the
priest going to put together some
solution to find out whether she uh
committed adultery or not but keep
reading what ver are you verse
16 wa just keep reading and the priest
shall bring her near and set her before
the Lord and the priest shall take holy
water in the earth and vessel and of the
dust that is in the floor of the
Tabernacle the priest shall take it and
put it into the water and the priest
shall set the
woman now see this this solution you can
read the rest of it on your own this
solution if the woman is guilty if the
woman is not guilty won't nothing happen
but if the woman is guilty then a b
would swell and a thigh would r
well let's see what the pre what the
woman had the priest had to do with the
woman before he gave her this
solution read Verse
18 and the priest shall set the woman
before the Lord and uncover the woman's
head and put the offering of Memorial in
her hands which is the jealousy
offering he's going to do what with her
head
it's gonna uncover the woman's head and
put the offering of Memorial in her
hands
now if if a covered head was not the
custom then why this woman had her head
covered and so the head COV was a
protection because he was under the
protection of a man that's what the head
COV meant
right as long as she had the head cover
on this solution wouldn't have worked
but when you take the head coven off
then that mean that she was exposed of
whatever happened that's why the priest
had to uncover her head to a head
covering was a custom in Israel for the
woman that's all I have to
say all right I hope that answered your
question there as we continue to move on
to our next I'm moving on mici shur also
have two questions number one is it okay
to be cremated and two if a person is
not baptized in jesus' name will he not
inherit the
Kingdom all right dealing with the first
question is it okay to be cremated yeah
it's okay to be
cremated actually it's very popular
these days but let's go back to Genesis
the uh third chapter and show what it is
that cremation does Genesis 3
and when you get there brother let's
pick it up at that verse let's read nine
and 10 first because this is the Lord
talking here and I want to pick that up
Genesis 3 read n and 10 then we go skip
go ahead and the Lord God called unto
Adam and said unto him where are thou
and he said I heard thy voice voice in
the garden and I was afraid because I
was naked and I he myself all right so
this is when Adam got in trouble in the
garden of Eve he listened to Eve and he
was um he realized what nakedness was
and God knew that he had been talking to
the serpent but let's skip down and this
is what cremation does to you in verse
19 go ahead in the sweat of thy face
shall thou eat bread till thou return
unto the ground for out of it was thou
taken for dust thou are and unto dust
thou shall return so cremation is like a
a speed up of returning you to dust but
you a dust anyway and pration is popular
a lot of people are doing it now and uh
don't see anything wrong with it that's
all I got on that
question now we can go what's the second
one sister Deborah uh the second one is
uh if a person is not baptized in jesus'
name will he not inherit the
Kingdom no we can't say that you know
we've had so many generations and
thousand thousands of years are being
taught wrong but let's go and see let's
go into second Corinthians the 5th
chapter 2 Corinthians 5 that's why it's
so important for you to find the truth
and to walk therein right tanzel yes sir
second Corinthians
5 and read that verse seven and then we
going to skip down go ahead brother for
we walk by faith not by sight yes we do
we walk by faith not by sight some
people didn't know about um being
baptized in Jesus name which is the
correct way people went got baptized the
name of the father son and the excuse me
in the Holy Ghost and those are titles
so we can't go along with that one but
skip down about whether or not if
somebody had died and they were not
baptized in jesus' name would they not
inherit the Kingdom we can't say that
but I can read on who will say verse 10
and that'll be it go ahead well we must
all appear before the Judgment seat of
Christ and everyone may receive the
things done in his body according to
that he hath done whether it be good or
bad and that's the only answer I got for
that that um that's going to be up to
the Lord at the time of judgment because
everybody got to appear before the
judgment seat and be judged according to
the things that they have done and
that's in the hands of the Lord and
that's all I get
right all right we hope that answered
your question there and we continue to
move on moving on Straight Talk says if
I look at Christmas movies am I
wrong so Julius if you check out some
Christmas movies is that
wrong no it's not wrong you can look at
whatever you want to look at but in all
your getting get you
understanding how you going to if if you
don't look at it you going to read
Jeremiah the 10th chapter which tells
you about the Christmas tree and Satan
the devil knows how to Market
paganism so therefore you go watch what
you want to watch but don't do what they
do right because sometime that's how you
get educated on watching programs yeah
that's how you learn about these things
then you go to the Bible and you see uh
what you should do about these program
because that's what it is Sayan the
devil knows how to Market programming
it's paganism but it's marketing so now
let me give you one scripture that you
can uh use uh to support what the books
say let's go to First John the 4th
chapter brother
tenzel some sometime I watch movie to
see uh especially Biblical movies to see
how far if there if it's accurate or how
far how much is wrong right and this is
why I do
it uh 1 John 4 give me verse one
brother beloved believe not every Spirit
but try the spirit whether they are of
God because many false prophets are gone
out into the world and this why I say
Satan knows how to Market death he knows
how to Market paganism and that he knows
how to program the people people try the
spirits but you got to read the Bible to
see how accurate these programs are the
Bible does not give a birth date of
Christ but yet the world in these
programs says December the 25th and they
say Merry Christmas the Bible tells you
about the Christmas tree that these
programs have in there about to bowing
down and worshiping them with their
presence and so on and so forth so
therefore you got to try to Spirit
whether they be of Christ these
Christmas programs are not of Christ
it is of Satan the devil verse three and
I'm done go ahead brother and every
spirit that confesses not that Jesus
Christ is comment in the flesh is not of
God uhuh and this is that Spirit of
antichrist uhuh whereof ye have heard
that it should come and even now already
it is it in the world and the number one
two that the devil uses is deception so
the world uh is G a birth date it's
given a Christmas tree it's given uh
they took the word uh from H holy day
and they put made it a holiday so
therefore it is not of God I tried the
spirit and I found out to be Pagan but
you could watch whatever you want to
watch but in all you're getting get you
understanding that's all I got I hope
that
helped yes sir that's correct and like
you said brother Julius in that verse 6
at the end of it once you get some
knowledge of the truth then hereby know
we the spirit of truth and the spirit of
error and there you go thank you brother
all right brother you welcome hope that
answered their question as we continue
to move on moving on Valencia wants you
to explain 1 corini 9 vers 19-
21 all right brother Dre what you say
about that 1 Corinthians 9:19 through
21 let go to uh 1 Corinthians 9 and
we'll start at 19 brother tanzel when
you get it go ahead and read
it for though I be free from all men yet
have I made myself service unto all that
I might gain the more Paul saying I'm
I'm not in bondage to no man but I'm a
servant of all that I may gain all the
more go
ahead and unto the Jews I became as a
Jew that I might gain the Jews to them
that are under the law as under the law
that I might gain them that the law yes
to them that are without law as without
law being not without law to God but
under the law to Christ that I might
gain them that are without
law go ahead until the weat became I as
weat that I might gain the weat I am
made all things to all men that I might
by all means save some so whatever
position man is in Paul is saying hey
I'm I'm meeting them where they're
at in that verse when he says to them
that are without law as without law but
not without law to God being not with
law to God but under the law of Christ
that I might gain those that are without
law so we're meeting people where they
at and we dealing with them but we
keeping the word of God Paul is not
saying he's not keeping the word of God
he's just simply saying I'm meeting them
where they at I hope that
helps yes sir brother brother Dre we do
that for the gospel's sake don't we for
the gospel's sake brother yes sir thank
you for that hope that answered their
question as we move on to our next one
moving on shalot T ask are we allowed to
have bald or fade type
haircuts bald or fade type haircuts gu
call
them well there's nothing in the Bible
that promotes it or condemns
it but we can't tell you whether you're
allowed or not you're not written in the
book whether you uh uh uh uh should or
should not so there's nothing in the
Bible against it
So my answer is apparently it's no
problem don't have to
say all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next
moving on Jain says please help me
understand obadah 1 verse
specifically shed light on the term
saviors all right Obadiah 1 and
21 that's the book we got Jose Joel Amos
and then Obadiah and brother Jerome what
you
say let's go read
it Dia verse
one chapter one one chapter verse
21 and savior shall come up on Mount
Zion to judge the Mount of Esau and the
kingdom shall be the
Lords these saviors are are those that
uh going to be in the first uh
Resurrection uh and they going to come
up on Mount
Zion they goingon to meet the Lord in
the air and they all going to come right
back
down to this earth you know uh let's go
to Zechariah 14 and then we going to do
re 20 also
Tel Zechariah 14:
1-5 go ahead when you get it behold the
day of the Lord cometh and thy spoil
shall be divided in the midst of thee
why will gather all nations against
Jerusalem to battle and the city shall
be taken and the hous is rifle and the
women ravish and half of the city shall
go forth captivity
and the residue of the people shall not
be cut off from the city then shall the
Lord go forth and fight against those
Nations as when he fought in the day of
battle and his Feast shall stand in that
day upon the Mount of olive which is
before Jerusalem on the East and the
Mount of oliv shall cleave in the midst
thereof towards the east and towards the
west and there shall be a very great
valley half of the mountain shall remove
toward the North and half of it toward
the South and ye shall flee to the
Valley of the mountains for the Valley
of the mountains shall reach unto Asel
yeah ye shall flee like as ye fled from
before the earthquakes in the days of
Uzziah king of Judah and the Lord my God
shall come and all the saints with thee
yeah and that Lord in that verse is
talking about Jesus Christ uh let's go
to that Revelations 20 and read verse
four and I saw throne and they that sat
upon them and judgment was given unto
them and I saw the souls of them that
were beheaded for the witness of Jesus
and for the word of God and which had
not worshiped the Beast neither his
image neither have received his Mark
upon their forehead or in their hands
and they lived and reign with Christ a
thousand years yeah so those are the
saviors that you wrote read about in
that 21st verse of obad
that's all I got
on all right thank you for that brother
hope that answer that question next
question with the time Check Yes uh the
time is
7:59 and uh Adam says my wife and family
continues to put a Christmas tree up in
the house I have explained the truth
about it being Pagan and nothing to do
with Christ it's frustrating do I
continue to leave by
example all right so a little rebellion
in the house guest
caller well the whole thing is if you
demanded the house then you supposed to
run your
house you run your house then ain't
nobody going to put no Christmas tree up
in it your wife children and nobody else
because you are the man of the house and
you're the head if you allow it then it
is on you now a family that don't live
with you or your family don't live with
you and they put the Christmas tree up
in their house then that's on
them but if you the head in your
household don't on Christmas tree go up
in your house simple as that all have to
say all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to the next next
one nley Charles asks about what does
Zechariah 13: 8 and9
mean Zechariah 13: 8-9 let's go there
brother
tanzel and when you get there read that
verse 8 and N in Zechariah 13 and the
guest caller we'll take it from
there and this shall come to pass that
in all the land sayeth the Lord two pars
therein shall be cut off and die but the
third shall be left therein and I will
bring the third part to the fire and
will refine them as silver is refine and
will try them as gold is try and they
shall call on my name and I will hear
them and I will say it is my people and
they shall say the Lord is my
God
89 zear 138 and9
okay well the Lord is this is this is uh
this is talking about the time of uh uh
Jesus read a there something in there
that said he going to Smite the
Shepherd in verse
seven well I missed that read it
again await oh sword against my shepherd
and against the man that is my
fellow okay now finish it read the rest
live
again sayeth the Lord of Hope Smite the
shepherd and the Sheep shall be
scattered and I will turn my hand upon
the little ones and it shall come to
pass that in all the land say the Lord
two parts therein shall be cut off and
die but the third shall be left therein
and I will bring the third part through
the fire and I will refine them as
silver is refined and will try them as
gold is Tred and they shall call on my
name and I will hear them and I will say
it is my people and they shall say the
Lord is my
God now what is telling you there that
in the days of Jesus that's it's time uh
Israel that they going to uh uh uh
crucify
Jesus then the Lord's going to turn on
his
Apostles and they going to be driven out
of the land and the day going to come
they going to be returned turn let's go
to Mark 14th
chapter read verse 26-
27 then we going to
skip 26 and 27
first Mark 14 verse
26 and when they had sung and hymn they
went out into the Mount of Olive and
Jesus said unto them all ye shall be
offended because of me this night for it
is written I will Smite the shepherd and
the Sheep shall be
scattered now see that dates the time
when in Zechariah 13th chapter 1389 is
start starting because that started in
Jesus time he going to Smite the
shepherd and uh and the Sheep going to
be
scattered and uh what was that verse 27
did you finish that yeah SK down to
verse 43 now and see what happened
and immediately while he yet spake
cometh Judas one of the 12 and with him
a great multitude with swords and stain
from the chief priests and the scribes
and the
elders now let's see what happened when
they took when when uh they come out
there and got Jesus skip down to verse
50 and they all forsook him and
fled so the whole thing is this talking
about Jesus
because his his his Apostle scattered
from it now let's skip down and Jesus
was telling you that this was going to
happen before it happened let's go into
Luke the 19th
Chapter and read
verses 41-
44 and when he was come near he beheld
the city and wept over it saying and
thou H has known even thou at least in
this thy day the things which belong
unto thy peace but now they are here
from thy eyes for the day shall come
upon thee that thy enemy shall cast a
trench about thee and Compass thee round
and keep thee in on every side and shall
lay thee even with the ground and thy
children within thee and thy shall not
leave in thee one stone upon another
because thou knewest not that time of
thy visit
a now Jesus saw what was going to happen
to Jerusalem and this happened in 7 ad
the Romans came and they TR cast a a
trench in fact they they dug a trench
and and build a levy around Jerusalem to
keep them from getting out and they and
and uh they destroyed
Jerusalem and they was crucified up to
500 people a day on the crosses the Lord
killed a whole lot of them whatever the
amount is this must be what Zachariah
was talking about but let show you when
that
happen
talking Luke
21 Luke and read read from 20 to 28
and when ye shall see Jerusalem the path
with army then know that the Desolation
thereof is nine then let them which are
in Judea flee to the mountains and let
them which are in the midst of it depart
out and let not them that are in the
countries enter there into for these be
the days of Vengeance that all things
may be
fulfilled for woe unto them that are
with child and to them that give suck in
those days but there shall be great
distress in the land and wrath upon this
people and they shall fall by the edge
of the sword and shall be led away
captiv to All Nations and Jerusalem
shall be trien down of the Gentiles
until the time of the Gentiles be
fulfilled now that happened that had
happened after Jesus had been
crucified then about later Jerusalem was
spitten by the edge of the sword and
that's when they crucified all the
people and they destroyed Jerusalem down
to the ground and then they were
scattered Jerusalem was scattered among
the among the uh uh uh Nations until the
times of the gentille be fulfilled and
the times of the Gentile are still going
on this happened in 7 ad since 7 ad
there have never been a uh a people that
called uh Israel have never been
established as a people we've been
slaved ever since a captive but the Lord
said he going to return a percentage
keep
reading and there shall be a sign in the
Sun and in the moon and in the stars and
upon the Earth distress of nations with
perplexity to see and the waves roaring
and man's Hearts failing them for fear
and for looking after those things which
are come on the earth for the powers of
Heaven shall be
shaken and then shall they see the son
of man coming in the clouds with power
and great glory and when these things
begin to come to pass then look up and
lift up your heads for your Redemption
jth
not now Zechariah then Zechariah is
talking about the time that just that
just name when Jesus going to come and
when he going to get crucified the
apostles going to be scattered Jerusalem
going to be
destroyed and a lot of Jews going to get
killed during that destruction in 7 ad
and then after that we were
scattered all over the Mediterranean and
from there all over the world and when
the Lord come that's when he going to
return us back to the land that is what
Zachariah is talking about that's all I
have to say all
right hope that answered your question
question is we continue to move on to
our next
question all right our next
question is going to be in first
Corinthians 6
and2 and if the Saints are the ones that
make it into
heaven what world would they be judging
if everyone is either in heaven or in
the L
brother Julius what you say about
that that is talking about the world of
come but Cornel uh
um this whole scripture well this this
scripture is talking about the end the
world to come tzel let's go and read
that and 1 Corinthians 6 we going to
read two and three and then we going to
move quickly
brother this is talking about the world
to
come and in other words when the Lord
returns
during a thousand years well go ahead
brother 1 Corinthians 6 2 and 3 go ahead
who do you not know that the Saints
shall judge the world and if the world
shall be judged by you are ye unworthy
to judge the smallest matters uhhuh know
ye not that we shall judge Angels but
how much more things that pertain to
this life you can't judge Angels right
now because angels are stronger than we
are they are Spirit beings you can't do
nothing to them and the were evil ones
you can't even see so therefore this is
talking about the world to come know you
not that you shall judge Angels you know
and it's going it's going to happen but
this is a old prophecy this is a a old
prophecy that's yet to be fulfilled
let's go to Psalm 122
brother Psalm 122 122 and we going um
read verses 1 and two and then we going
to skip Tel Psalm 122 because when the
Lord is going to come he going to come
back to the Mount of OLS in Jerusalem
that is where he left and that is where
feet going to touch in that day Psalm
122 1 and2 go ahead brother I was glad
when he said unto me let us go into the
house of the Lord where that's going to
be continue our feet shall stand within
thy Gates oh Jerusalem our feet shall
stand within thy Gates oh Jerusalem
because when the Lord come be coming
back to Jerusalem skip down to verse
four and five and go ahead what whether
the tribes go up whether the tribes go
up the tribes the 12 tribes of Israel go
ahead the tribes of the Lord yes to the
testimony of Israel uhuh to give thanks
unto the name of the Lord what's there
brother read it for there I set Thrones
of judgment the Thrones of the House of
David because he said for there where at
Jerusalem there's going to be set
Thrones of judgment now let's go to
Matthew the 19th chapter and let's look
at Jesus tell us in the flesh while he
was in his flesh Matthew 19 and read
verse 27 and 28 Matthew
1927-28 go
ahead then answer ped and said unto him
behold we have forsaken all and follow
thee so what shall we have therefore
uhhuh and Jesus said unto them verily I
say unto you that ye which have followed
me in the gener and a regeneration when
the son of man shall sit in the Throne
of his glory he shall also shall sit
upon 12 Thrones judging the 12 tribes of
Israel we read about them tribe the 12
tribes right there where the tribes go
up in Psalm 122 didn't we so everything
is in order let's go to my last place
Revelation the 20th
chapter Revelation the 20th chapter
and just read verse
four Revelation 20 and just verse four
Satan is put away for a thousand years
and go ahead in verse four and I saw
Thrones and they that set upon them and
judgment was given unto them they're not
in the Judgment they are the judges they
are the judges go ahead and I saw the
souls of them that were beheaded for the
witness of Jesus and for the word of God
uhuh which had not worshiped the Beast
neither his image neither had received
his Mark upon their foreheads or in
their hands and they lived and reigned
with Christ a thousand years so now that
is the world of come but part of your
question is said uh one of your if the
Saints are the ones that make it into
heaven the Bible don't teach going to
heaven my last scripture John 3 and13
Let's see what Jesus said
that's why he going to come from Heaven
he went back to heaven and he going to
come from
Heaven John 3 and13 and we have a lesson
that is entitled The Dead where are they
Heaven hell or the grave John 3 and13
Look what Jesus said go ahead and no man
have ascended up to heaven but he that
came down from heaven even the son of
man which is in heaven
so never from Genesis to revelation
nobody ascends up into the heaven of
Heavens which is the third heaven except
Jesus that came down from there so this
is talking about the world to come
that's going and where the Saints are be
are going to be the
judges and know ye not that you shall
judge angels that is the world of come
that's all I got I hope that
helped yes sir thank you for that yes
caller yes caller go right
ahead let's go in 149 chapter the psalm
and we're going to read verse
one and when you read verse one then you
skip down and start at verse five and
continue the
nine
49 and verse
one praise ye the Lord sing unto the
Lord a new song and his praise in the
congre congregation of saints
and praise ye the Lord and you know and
sing a new song of his praise of the
congregation of the Saints skip down to
verse five and continue let the Saints
be joyful in glory let them sing aloud
upon their
beds let the high praises of God be in
their mouth and a two-edged sword in
their hand to execute vengeance upon the
Heathen and Punishment upon the people
yes sir to buy their kings with chains
and their nobles with feathers of ir
to execute upon them the Judgment
written this honor have all his Saints
praise ye the Lord yes sir that's why
Saints going judge the world like Julia
said the world will come the Thousand
Year Millennium period but we gonna help
Jesus run this whole
earth all I have to
say thank you all right hope that
answered your question and it's a
beautiful thing to be on the side of the
Lord all right right moving on to our
next question moving on Malik Shakur
says so it's okay to celebrate
Thanksgiving but not Christmas aren't
they both
Pagan all right guess
caller yes caller
and what was the question I missed it
for some reason my other phone
wrong right uh the question is so it's
okay to celebrate Thanksgiving but not
Christmas aren't they both
Pagan when it comes to uh uh uh when it
comes to what we should celebrate and
what we should not we have to deal with
with what the Bible
say and so the Bible speaks against
Christmas and We Know It clearly because
it talks about the Christmas tree let's
go into Jeremiah the 10th
chapter read verses
1-5 read it when you get
there hear ye the word which the Lord
speaketh unto you oh House of Israel
thus sayeth the Lord learn not the way
of the heath and be not dismayed at the
signs of Heaven for the Heathen are
dismayed at them for the custom of the
people are vain for one cut a tree out
of the forest the work of the hands of a
Workman with the axe they deck it with
silver and with gold they fasten it with
nails and with hammers that it move not
they are upright as the palm tree but
speak not they must needs be born
because they cannot go be not afraid of
them for they cannot do evil neither
also it is in them to do
good now that defines
Christmas and the Bible just Define that
we know it's Pagan so the Pagan is what
the Bible call
Pagan so I don't see nothing in the
Bible it is called Thanksgiving Pagan it
don't uphold it neither does it condemn
it so as far as Thanksgiving concerned
the Civil holiday and nothing in the
Bible said I shall not do it but it tell
you specifically not to keep Christmas
that's all they have to
say all right hope that aned your
question as we move on to our next next
one Israel tried asked Can
you can a person receive salvation on
his dying
bed sure it's possible I
mean uh the thief he received salvation
and he was on his dying cross right so
you know we can't um say that that's not
possible because it is but let's go to
Romans the 9th chapter Romans
9 Romans
N9 and let's pick it up at that verse
14 because even on your dying bed hey to
be in the hands of the Lord is the best
place to
be Romans 9:14 and 15 and then we go
skip go ahead
brother what shall we say then is there
unrighteousness with God
God for he have said to Moses I will
have mercy on whom I will have mercy and
I will have compassion on whom I will
have compassion yeah so Lord hey is no
unrighteousness with him all the
decisions he make is correct and so
therefore he was saying to Moses that he
will have mercy on whom he will have
mercy and compassion on whom he will
have compassion even when someone's on
their dying bed or may even be breathing
their last breath skip down to 33 and
read as it is written behold like Al lay
in Zion a stumbling stone and rock of
offense and whosoever Believe on him
shall not be ashamed yes and that is the
key to believe on him but I tell you one
thing when you're on your dying bed or
when you're at your last breath here's
somebody that's great to know turn back
to Isaiah
44 Isaiah
44 that's why while we have this breath
we need to be seeking out this God right
now because ain't nobody bad like him
Isaiah
44 read that verse six for me brother
and then we go
skip thus sayeth the Lord the king of
Israel and his Redeemer the Lord of
hosts I am the first and I am the last
and besides me there is no God that's a
great God to know right brother tan yes
sir he said there is no other God beside
him and he even tells us read that verse
eight go ahead fear ye not neither be
afraid have not I told thee from that
time and have declared it ye are even my
Witnesses is there a god besides me yeah
there is no God I know not any so if the
Lord don't know any God that's bad like
him then hey we need look no further
skip down brother and read that verse um
24 for me and that'll be it go
ahead thus sayth the Lord thy Redeemer
and he that formed thee from the womb I
am the Lord that maketh all things that
stretches forth the heavens alone that
spread abroad the Earth by myself so
this is the greatest god to know the one
that says he is the Lord and he is the
king of Israel because with your last
breath hey he is a merciful god he is
kind and wonderful and no better hands
to be than him so yeah it's possible to
receive salvation even when you're on
your dying bed and that's all I
got and we hope that that ansed your
question as we move on to our next
moving on norless tape is following up
from uh the answer given from last week
question which
was why can't the soul mentioned in
Matthew 10 verse 28 be killed by them
men if it is a body flesh and blood so
the followup question now is that he's
in
is fear not them which kill the body
flesh and blood but aren't able to kill
the soul flesh and blood does that make
sense doesn't the word both being you
show
distinction between body and soul and
Matthew 10 verse 28 is still given
right Dre what you
say yeah I say let's go back to that
Matthew 28 we're going to take a a real
good look at that and I think I think
the issue comes into play is that you're
looking at this body that he's talking
about
killing as a flesh and blood body he is
not talking about a flesh and blood body
so let's go to Matthew 10 read that
verse 28 brother go ahead
and fear not them which kill the body
but are not able to kill the soul rather
fear him which is able to destroy both
soul and Body in hell now he's he's
saying fear him which is able to destroy
both soul and Body in Hell well we read
last week that the soul and the body is
one and the same but I want you to pay
attention to the next verse verse 29 go
ahead are not Two Sparrows sold for a
furthering and one of them shall not
fall on the ground without your father
now that has nothing to do with the
question that we're reading because it's
going into something else but I read
this because I wanted you to know that
Luke gives the same account and I want
us to go to Luke 12 Luke 12
now because we're not we're not talking
about a flesh and blood body that God is
going to
heal that you should fear Him let's go
to Luke
12 and we are going to pick that up at
verse 4 Luke 12
and4 go ahead brother and I say unto you
my friends be not afraid of them that
killed the body and after that have no
more that they can do notice he didn't
say nothing about Soul here he says my
friends I say unto you be not afraid of
them that can kill that kill the body
and after that there's no more that they
can do because they Flesh and Blood
people don't have the power to raise you
up and kill you again with the second
death God got that power that's what you
remember verse five brother go ahead but
I will forarm you whom ye shall fear
fear Him which after he have killed have
power to cast into hell yeah I say unto
you fear Him that's who you should here
the one that can kill you raise you up
and kill you again with a Everlasting
death a second death now let's go to
Revelation uh 20
Revelation
20 Revelation 20 and verse 11 Revelation
20 and 11 I want us to look at that go
ahead brother when you get
it and I saw a great white throne and
him that sat on it from whose face of
the earth and the heavens fled away and
there was found no place for
them and I saw dead small and great
stand before God and the books were open
and another book was open which is The
Book of Life and the dead were judged
out of those things which were written
in the books according to their
works and the Sea gave up the dead which
were in it and death and H delivered up
the dead which were in them and they
were judged every man according to their
works and death and hell were cast into
the Lake of Fire this is the second
death is the second death this is the
death that you don't want no part of and
if you fear God and keep his
Commandments you won't be a part of that
but he is not talking about a flesh and
blood body now First Corinthians 15 vers
35 all the way to 54 will explain that
perfectly for you because this body
Bears grain you have a corruptible body
but you will have an Incorruptible body
that won't burn up that won't die that
you can scream help and cry out but it's
gonna still be in Everlasting
punishment if you don't do what God
say so this is not talking about a flesh
and blood body this is talking about a
body that will live forever and be
punished a spirit spiritual body right
please read that 1 Corinthians
1535 to 54 and it will bless you it will
help you to understand that that's
that's all I got with that if anybody
else would like to
add yeah i' like to throw something in
this question keep coming up because the
real question is being the statement is
being made here is that you have a that
the body and the Soul are two different
things this is what going
on I want to go to two places because uh
and and because whoever this person is
they want to make us have a body a soul
and a soul inside the body but let's go
into in Hebrews the 10th
chapter right and read the uh uh uh we
going to read verse
one and then we're going to read verse
four and five and we're going to skip
down and read 10
because this need to be laid to
rest
Hebrews that's the real thing that's
being said that we got a body a soul
inside of it go ahead and read it 10 and
one for the law having a shadow of good
things to come and not the very image of
the things can never with those
sacrifices with they offer Year bye
continually make the comers there unto
perfect get down to verse four and fire
for it is not possible that the blood of
bulls and of ghost should take away sin
wherefore when he cometh into the world
he said sacrifice and offering thou
wouldest not but a body has thou
prepared
me now skip down to 10 and let's see
what he going to do with that
body by the which will we are Sanctified
through the offering of the body of
Jesus Christ once for
all now we are Sanctified through the
off of the body of Jesus Christ once and
for
all so we call his him a body his his
his body a body right right Isaiah 53r
chapter yes sir and read verse 10
because it's talking about Jesus right
here okay in fact read verse five and
then we and then we're going to skip
down to verse 10 to let you know this
talking about Jesus 5 3 and 5 Isaiah 53
but he was wounded for our transgression
and he was bruised for our iniquities
the chastisement of our peace was upon
him and with his stripes we are healed
we know they talking about Jesus don't
we right
y so skip down verse 10 and see what it
says yet it pleased the Lord to bruise
him and he ha put him to grief but Thou
shalt make his soul an offering for sin
make his soul an offer for sin Hebrews
the 10th chapter say his body was made
an offer for sin isn't that correct
right the W offered his body out of
Soul both of because the body is the
soul and I don't think we should deal
with this
anymore
right all
right in Genesis 2:7 the first man made
first man was made a living son
tell you the first Corinthians 15th
chapter that the first Adam was made a
living Soul that's right I think we we
done deal with this enough yes sir y all
right so we hope that you was able to
see the light with that and we will be
moving on from that question but Deborah
what is our next question uh yes the
next question is from uh Janie do uh
that says uh this is a follow up to last
sweet question and Janie doe thanks for
uh thank you all for your response but
she still is kind of lary so she says so
if I were to sell stop sister de hold on
one second did we uh did we miss a
question
there the one right before Janie
do uh yes it was
ah and they wanted know what does the
verses in Joel
3 vers 8 and
17 all right brother Jerome say share
some light on that Joel
3 verses 8 and verse
17 and let's go read
it when you get it Joy
um when you get it Tel go ahead and read
it Joel 3 verse 8 and 17 can you can you
just do eight and then I'll I'll I'll
kind of address eight and then we'll
read this 17 afterwards
okay go ahead and I will sell your sons
and daughters into the hand of the
childrens of Judah and they shall sell
them to the seian savans to a people far
off for the Lord has spoken
it okay um let's go look at um Isaiah
the 14th chapter verse
1-3 it's the same thing that uh Nations
have done with God's people and and and
and having them serve in hard bondage
and and captivity you know the Lord
going to turn that thing around but
Israel when
they are ruling and on top they ain't
gonna make them people serve
with hard bondage but still they gonna
be servants to Israel
okay all let's go to uh Isaiah 14 read
verse 1
through3 for the Lord will have mercy on
Jacob and will yet choose Israel and set
them in their own land and the strangers
shall be joined with them and they shall
cleave to the house of
Jacob and the people shall take them and
bring them in their place and the house
of Israel shall possess them in the land
of the Lord for servants and handmaids
and they shall take them captives who
captive they were and they shall rule
over their
oppressors it shall come to pass in the
day that the Lord shall give thee rest
from thy sorrows and from thy fear and
from the hard bondage wherein thou was
made to
serve yeah and so in that verse eight
that Joel it talked about how uh they
would sell them to the sons their sons
and daughters into the hand of the
children of Judah and they should sell
them to the savans you know so Israel
May are going to decid and and on
occasion to you know put them in the
hand of the sabians and the sabians
going to do what they will as far as
being servants to the savings you know
so now let's deal with that uh 17 verse
in that
Joel so shall ye know that I am the Lord
your God dwelling in Zion my Holy
Mountain then shall Jerusalem be holy
and there shall no strangers pass
through her anymore yeah and
that you understand that better if we go
if we tie that to
Ezekiel uh 47th chapter concerning the
stranger
E when they become when they become when
they when they be blessed to sojourn
with the children of Israel in their in
their inheritance and in their
possessions look what Ezekiel 4 say say
about the strangers concerning the
inheritance read verse 21 to
23 so ye so shall ye divide this land
unto you according to the tribes of
Israel this shall come to pass that ye
shall divide it by lot for inheritance
unto you and to the strangers that s
journ among you which shall beg got
children among you and they shall be
unto you as born in the country among
the children of Israel and they shall
have inheritance with you among the
tribes of Israel yeah so let me say this
let me say this so they were strangers
say they were Europeans Gentiles but
then if they be blessed to dwell with
Israel it a they going to be just like
one that's born in the land and then
whichever among whichever tribe that
they be pleased to dwell among you have
to get them an
inheritance so can you pick that up
again 2022 on down to 23 and it shall
come to pass that ye shall divide it by
life for inheritance unto you and to the
stranger that sour among you which shall
be got children among you and they shall
be unto you as born born in the country
among the children of
Israel they shall have inheritance with
you among the tribes of Israel and it
shall come to pass and in what tribe The
Strangers sourth there shall ye give him
his inheritance sayeth the Lord God yeah
so now they won't be strangers no more
they gonna be like one born in the
land that's all I got if anybody want to
add
something all right thank you for that
there brother and uh hope that they was
able to see the light on that as we move
on sister Devil with a Time Check Yes
the time is
8:40 uh now I'm getting to Janie doe
that is a followup to the last week
question uh so she says so if I were to
sell or stock holiday Goods as a
cashier I wouldn't be violating the
first first commandment and Matthew 6
verse
24 also could you give me an example of
someone in the Bible who adapted his
religion belief to remain employed I
just want to be absolutely sure that I'm
not sinning against God she
says all right I think we will was we
gave you a pretty good answer last time
so first of all remember that's that's
not your store you're are an employee
there at that store and you are doing a
job open to the P yes sir go ahead
brother yes sir look there somebody can
find this where Elisha heal this uh this
uh uh Syrian uh uh captain from his
leprosy
all right and see what and this and then
what this guy said about the when I go
uh uh to the
king and he praying before his God God
and you know and he holding my hand I
want you to know that I'm doing my job
any other can somebody find that that's
Second Kings the 5th
chapter uh pick it up at verse
one second Kings the fth chapter
in verse one I believe so
yeah all
right
yeah okay so go ahead tanzel let's pick
it up
there
okay well you want to get to the last
part of or read the whole
story well well the whole thing is this
Syrian Captain he's a great and he was a
leper and and he and he listen to heal
him okay right I want to show you what
he said after he had been healed about
having to go and uh uh with his with his
boss the king that's verse 17 and
18 verse 17 and 18 yes sir now this guy
feared the god of Israel because the God
had healed him from his leprosy so he
wanted to let the let the uh the uh
Prophet know
and and also God that look I ain't
serving this guy's God read
it and neon said shall there not then I
pray thee be given to thy servant to
musees burden of Earth for thy servant
will henceforth offer neither burnt
offerings nor sacrifice unto other gods
but unto the
Lord but this thing the Lord paren thy
servant that when my master goeth into
the house of Ron to worship there and
and he leanth on my hand and I bow
myself in the house of raymon when I bow
down myself in the house of Raymond the
Lord pardon th servant in this
thing see he's going in now he is not
serving this his his King's God that is
his job you understand what I'm saying y
j i want you to know I'm going to read
it again in this thing the Lord pardon
thy servant that when my master see when
he said pardon thy servant that tell you
he's a servant of God now ain't it
yep that when my master goeth into the
house of Rama which is a pagan God to
worship him there and he leanth on my
hand and I bow myself in the house of
Rama when I bow down myself in the house
of Rama let the Lord pardon thy servant
in this thing because he is just doing
his job you understand yes sir excellent
scripture huh yeah yep that's it he is
not so now one other place I think a
soldier when Jesus was on the cross the
soldier asked Jesus what should he
do somebody can pull that
up and he told him uh uh you know be
satisfied with your wages something on
that
order all right we search more for that
do I want this person to write this
scripture down so won't call next
week all right got Luke Luke 3 and14
Luke 3
and4 that's it
Sean all right let's go to Luke 3 and
pick it up at the verse 14 Luke 3 and4
okay read it see what
it and the soldiers likewise demanded of
him saying and what shall we do and he
said unto them do violence to no man
neither accuse any falsely and be
content with your
wages so he's telling he didn't say stop
being a
soldier did he n no don't do no wrong to
no man you know CU you have to be a you
and be satisfied with your ways in other
words don't let nobody bribe
you to do somebody some harm that was
his job he was a soldier he had to do
what he was
told same thing with nean Captain you
know when I go in the guy and B out with
this guy I'm not serving this God he
called he called the god of Israel his
master what I'm doing is I'm just doing
my job and I want to say if that's not
good enough then
quit and don't come to me saying brother
can you spare me alone for my rent but
I'm not going to hear
you that's all I got to say yeah that's
it so we we hope that you were able to
glean some light from that and we
understand that you say that you don't
want to sin against God and there are
two scriptures right there to let you
know that you just doing the
job that's it all right so we going to
move on to our next question sister
Deborah because time is really starting
to get away yes we are now into
tonight's Q&A for Wednesday November the
27 2024 so philosophy
says uh I just want to be clear on the
meaning of leprosy in Mark 1 vers 40
through
43 there's different meanings to leprosy
it uh it was physical right and also why
did Jesus not want the man to spread the
news all right brother
Julius go ahead brother let's go to read
mark one and 40 and 43 yes it is
physical leprosy you had two types of
leprosy you had the unclean leprosy
which is a skin disease that affects the
the eyes the inner Linings of the nose
uh uh and it was like a uh uh sort of
like flesh eating or something like that
then you have a clean type of leprosy
which mean that you turned white but
this was an unclean leprosy go ahead and
read brother and there came a leper to
him beseeching him and kneeling down to
him and saying unto him if thou will
thou CEST make me
clean go ahead and Jesus moved with
compass and put forth his hand and
touched him and said unto him I will be
thou clean so go ahead and read and as
soon as as he has spoken immediately the
lepers departed from him and he was
cleansed so he was cleansed of the
disease called leprosy it's got a new
medical name today uh I can't call it
but I I I've read about it but go ahead
at verse
44 you want me read 43 uh yeah 43 and he
straightway charged him and forth withth
sent him away and what did he say to him
when he charged him go ahead and he said
unto him see thou say nothing to any man
but go thy way and show thyself to the
priest and offered for thy cleansing
those things which Moses commanded for a
testimony unto them so now so Jesus
healed this man that had a disease okay
this was an unclean lepy but why did he
tell the man not to tell nobody verse 45
the answer is right there in the next
verse go ahead but he went out and began
to publish it much and to blaze the bra
the master in so much that Jesus could
no more openly enter into the city but
was without in desert places and they
came to him from every quarter because
he didn't want nobody uh bum rushing him
so the book told you that the uh the man
tell everybody how Jesus had he him so
much that Jesus could not walk publicly
among people so so he said in so much
that Jesus could no more openly enter
into the city right but was outside in
desert place he had to go out to the
open places because the people thronged
him and they bum rushed him that's why
and they came to him from every quarter
when they found out where he was he was
he didn't want nobody to know all that
at that time that's the answer I hope
that helped so yes that was a physical
leprosy a
disease like you said brother one was
clean and one was unclean right
unclean means that you turn white like
Abraham put his bosom Lord turned his
hand white and then he put it back in
turned his regular skin color Miriam was
turned white a leprosy for seven lepos
for seven days but after that she came
back into the camp so this man has a
physical unclean
leprosy all right hope that answered
your question next question next
question the Le says can you tell me
what month was Jesus
born yes Cara can you share some light
on the month of Jesus
birth I can is not written no I can't
tell you right it's not in the
Bible yep and so we going to move on to
our next question yes next question
turkor pearls asked in Daniel 8 verse 22
two what are the four kingdoms
mentioned Daniel 8 let's go there Tel to
that Daniel
8 and verse
22 they while they going there I'm I'm
going to have to check out okay because
something else come up I got to deal
with okay okay brother all right all
right okay
so question again there
sister yes uh turquo uh pearls as in
Daniel 8 vers verse 22 what are the four
kingdoms
mentioned all right let's uh let's read
that and then we're going to open it up
to the
panel now that being broken whereas four
stood up for for it four kingdoms shall
stand up out of the Nations but not in
his
power all right what's those four
kingdoms there
brothers that's Babylon meor Persia
Greece and
Rome Y and those are your four kingdoms
right there
Babylonian Neo Persian Greek and
Rome all right sister Deborah we
moving yes uh Sean Leah asked in Isaiah
verse2 the scripture mention waste
places does this refer to the habitation
of the
homeless Isaiah
58 and ver verse 12
all
right why don't we go there and read
that go ahead
brother and they that shall be of thee
shall build the old W places and thou
shall raise up the foundations of many
generations and thou shall be called the
repairer of the breach the restorer of
path to dwell in
open to the
panel sound like uninhabited
places yeah and we know it's bigger than
being homeless right yep it's like it's
like uh the deserts of Las Vegas or
Phoenix
uninhabited they call it the
wastelands very good brother all right
we gonna move on to our next question
yes next question Miss way asked in
Romans
8 verse 16 What Spirit of man are they
talking about Romans 8 verse 16 What
Spirit of man are they talking about all
right why don't we go there and let's
read
that and let's pick it up tanzel because
um let's pick it up at at verse 12 and
read down
because we are not debt or we not in
debt to the flesh but we are in debt we
owe the spirit read verse 12 read down
and we'll open it up to the panel go
ahead therefore brethren we are deor not
to the flesh to live after the
flesh for if you live after the flesh
you shall die but if you through the
spirit do mortify the Deeds of your body
you shall
live for as many as are live by the
spirit of God they are the sons of
God ye have not received go ahead
brother for ye have not receed the
spirit of bondage again to fear but ye
have received the spirit of adoption
whereby we cry ABA father and was it
verse 16 in question Deborah yes and her
question again was what Spirit of man
are they talking about in Romans 8 verse
all right I know this verse 16 here is
talking about the word but go ahead and
read it brother when it say the spirit
the word itself beareth witness with our
spirit that we are the children of God
because it's the word that determines
whether or not we are walking with the
Lord if we are following his word and
keeping his laws statutes and
Commandments read it and then let's open
it up to the
P the spirit itself bear witness with
our spirit that we are the children of
God anybody on the panel like to add to
that it's the word that determines if we
servants what you say Jerome can we go
to um St John
17 all right read John 17 yeah and read
verse 19-
23 St John 17 19 to 23
and for their sake I sanctify myself
that they also might be Sanctified
through the
truth neither pray I for these alone but
for them also which Shall Believe on me
through their
word that they all may be one as thou
father are in me and I in thee that they
also may be one in us that the world may
believe that thou has sent
me and the glory was thou gavest me I
have given them that they may be one
even as we are
one i in them yeah and thou in me that
they may be made perfect and one that
the world may know that thou has sent me
and has loved them as thou has loved
me yeah and it's like Cornell said
through that word we all are one with
the Lord and the father that's right
that's that's of God or the word of God
that send you that agrees with the
written word that's all
right Y and that um and we in that John
17 right
[Music]
tanzel uh just read that verse
17 sanctify them through thy truth Thy
word is truth yep that's it yep and
thank you brother Jerome for that back
up we hope that answered your question
and Miss weight as we are coming up on
what appears to be our last question
sister Deborah what is it okay Orlando
day ask who are the four Carpenters that
are mentioned in Zechariah 1 verse
20 who are these four Carpenters
mentioned in that
Zachariah what verse sister Zechariah
what one verse
20 Zechariah 1 and
20 why don't we go there and read that
and then we're going to open it up to
the
panel all right
Zarah one vers start at verse 20 yes the
Lord showed me four
CS then said I what come these to do and
he spake saying these are the horns
which have scattered Judah so that no
man did lifted up his head these are
come to freay them to cast out the Horn
of the Gentiles which lifted up their
horn over the land of Judah to scatter
it all right open to the panel because
it looks like here when they said um
what come these to do and he spake
saying these are the horns which have
scattered Judah
and that ties into what you said earlier
brother Julius about Babylonian Meo
Persian Greek and Rome right them the
ones that scattered Judah those are the
wom scattered Jud Judah uh and these are
four angels that the Lord is uh using to
hold back uh World War I until the time
appointed just before Revelation 7th
chapter re aans 7 you want to go there
brother
yeah yeah go there and take a quick look
at that Revelation
7 and then we'll read one to three one
to three all
right okay go right ahead and after
these things I saw four Angels standing
on the four corners of the Earth holding
the Four Winds of the earth that the
wind should not blow on the earth nor on
the sea nor on any tree and I saw
another Angel ascending from the East
having the Seal of the Living God and he
cried with a loud voice to the four
angels to whom it was given to hurt the
earth and the Sea saying hurt not the
Earth neither the sea nor the tree till
we have sealed the Servants of our God
and their
forehead yep that's it brother that ties
right into that and um we hope that that
definitely answered that question
because the Lord needed needed them to
hold back cuz this man is set on
destruction is yes sir Lord need them
Angels kind of hold it back until he say
that it's time to let loose all right
sister de time check the time is
902 902 all right we have ran out of
time but we want to thank everybody from
all around the world who joined us this
evening we had fun participating with
you as a family and answering your
questions and we say if you submitted a
question and we didn't have a chance to
get to it please don't resubmit it says
to Deborah take your question should put
it in rotation and we will answer it
next week so until we all come together
again we ask that you please be safe out
there be blessed and may the Lord have
mercy on us all as brother tanzel closes
us
out Our Father which are in heaven
Hallowed be thy name
thy kingdom come thy will be done in
earth as it is in heaven give us this
day our daily bread and forgive us of
our debts as we forgive our debtors and
lead us not into temptation but Deliver
Us from Evil for thine is the kingdom
and the power and the glory forever in
Jesus name we pray amen amen amen good
night